

# Muoki

March 1993 • bonny.moki@gmail.com • +254740857767

### INTRO

I am a full stack Software Developer with skills in technical leadership, communication and presentations. Experienced in full project life cycle from design to implementation to integration. Expert in diverse programming languages, including PHP & its MVC frameworks (Laravel and Codelgniter), JavaScript (Jquery and React JS), .

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Software developer

PROWIZ TECHNOLOGIES • Mar 2020 - Present

I have been the sole developer of the following web applications

- 1. signval.com property valuation document signing. I was using codeigniter, Jquery and Mysql.
- 2. Mortgagekenya.com marketplace with both backend and frontend . I was using codeigniter, JQuery and Mysql.
- 3. valuationkenya.com valuation report submission platform to lenders . I was using Laravel 9 for the API, React Js and MUI, docker and github actions.

# **Lead Software Developer**

Dukapepe Ltd • Sep 2017 - Present

These have been my Tasks:-

- 1. Development and testing of Restful APIs in laravel and codeigniter.
- 2. Managing and improving existing mobile and web applications in Android.
- 3. Developing Function Specification documents for new changes and solutions.
- 4. Managing code and databases on AWS.
- 5. Deployment and testing of the specific applications .
- 6. Software Project Management using Jira.
- 7.User Training.
- 8 Design of Dukapepe Scalable and secure architecture on AWS.
- 9 MySQL Database management on AWS RDS.
- 10 CI/CD implimentation with codedeploy, Bitbucket and EC2 clients on AWS.

#### Intern

Technical University of Kenya • Jan 2016 - Mar 2016

While I was on attachment, I was able to : -

- Do Computer and network maintenance. \*
- Do content updates on http://gallery.tukenya.ac.ke

## **EDUCATION**

## **BSC**. Computer Science

Maseno University • Jan 2012 - Dec 2015

Some of the skills I acquired included :-

- 1. web and mobile application development.
- 2. Networks.
- 3. Transaction Databases.
- 4. Communication skills
- 5. Logics
- 6. Software Engineering



r other software version management systems) PHP Object oriented programming JavaScript

on programming interfaces (API) Github (or other software version management systems) PHP JavaScript

Application programming interfaces (API) JavaScript Application programming interfaces (API) Object oriented programming JavaScript

### **CERTIFICATES**

### LANGUAGES

**English** 

Spoken: Fluent • Written: Fluent

**Swahili** 

Spoken: Fluent • Written: Fluent

# **ASSOCIATIONS**

### HOBBIES

-Watching Movies.

- Farming.

# LINKS

https://bitbucket.org/Bonae/

https://github.com/BonfaceMuoki

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bonface-kyalo-a48250100

# REFERENCES